gadgetpics.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy - About ChaCha | About ChaCha

**Privacy Policy**

At ChaCha we recognize that your privacy is important to you. This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) applies to your use of the ChaCha websites (the “Site”) as well as any of the services, products, software and applications offered by ChaCha (the “Services”), including our online and mobile services.

This Privacy Policy summarizes ChaCha’s privacy practices and the uses of the information that ChaCha gathers via the Site and the Services. This Privacy Policy applies to ChaCha Search, Inc., subsidiaries and affiliates, its successors and assigns (collectively “ChaCha”). Please note that ChaCha may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and you should check this page periodically for changes. If changes are made, ChaCha will notify users by stating the date the Privacy Policy change is effective. If significant changes to the Privacy Policy are made, it will be prominently indicated on the Site.

**The Information ChaCha Collects and Uses**

In connection with your access to or use of the Site or the Services, ChaCha may request and/or collect from you personal information that may include: first and last name, address, phone number, email address, location or other information (”Personal Information”). By accessing or using the Site or the Services you are accepting the terms of ChaCha’s Privacy Policy.

Some of the Personal Information (for example your name and username) is listed publicly on chachee.heroku.com, me.chacha.com and ChaCha.me (collectively, the “ChaCha.me Service”), including on your profile page and in search results. The ChaCha.me Service is designed to help you receive answers and comments. Because most of the information you provide to the ChaCha.me Service is information you want made public, your questions and comments may be broadly and instantly disseminated. You should be careful about all information that may be made public by the ChaCha.me Service. When you submit information, you are transferring such information into the World Wide Web and you hereby consent to such transfer. Likewise, your replies to questions submitted via the ChaCha.me Service may be published to other websites. You are responsible for what gets published. Whatever you enter into the ChaCha.me Service text boxes may be published and could be publicly viewable immediately upon your clicking the submit button.

IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THE PRIVACY PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE CHACHA SITE OR SERVICES.

ChaCha may utilize the Personal Information collected for the purposes of providing, analyzing, personalizing or improving the Site or the Services, or developing new services.

ChaCha may share with third parties certain aggregated, anonymous, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched a particular category, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify any user individually.

ChaCha may but is not obliged to republish queries and answers which may be associated with geographic location information provided directly or indirectly by You. Republished queries are anonymous, and solely include content owned or licensed by ChaCha and a generalized location associated with the query which does not identify any individual.

ChaCha does not share Personal Information with other companies or individuals outside ChaCha except in the following limited circumstances:

  * We have your consent.
  * We may provide such Personal Information to affiliated companies or other trusted businesses for the purposes of processing Personal Information on our behalf. We require that these parties process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * ChaCha may request additional information from you on product order forms or other online transaction forms. Such forms may require you to provide contact information (such as name and mailing or shipping address) and payment information (such as credit card number and credit card expiration date). Information that you provide may be used for billing and accounting purposes, for recording products and services that you have licensed, bought or downloaded, and to fill your orders. ChaCha may use contact information to communicate with you about orders, products, services, or fees or charges. ChaCha may use an outside shipping company to ship orders and uses a credit card processing company to process payments for goods and services. These companies have access to user information in order to perform their functions.
  * ChaCha may partner with other third parties to provide specific goods or services. When you sign up for such goods or services, ChaCha will share names or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these goods or services. ChaCha does not authorize third party providers to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose related to these goods or services.
  * ChaCha may disclose your Personal Information in the good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable government request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Use including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of ChaCha, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.
  * When you send email or other communications to ChaCha, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve the Site and the Services.

**ChaCha does not knowingly collect or maintain Personal Information through the Site or the Services from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of the Site or the Services is directed to persons under 13.** If you are under 13 years of age, then please do not use or access the Site or the Services at any time or in any manner. If ChaCha learns that Personal Information of persons under 13 years of age has been collected through the Site or the Services without verified parental consent, then ChaCha will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

ChaCha may disclose and/or transfer your Personal Information to a buyer or transferee of all or a portion of its assets in conjunction with the sale or transfer of such assets; however, we will provide notice on our web site before Personal Information is transferred or becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Query and Session Logging**

ChaCha automatically records (or “logs”) all search queries or questions, the results of all search sessions and responses provided and any communications by, to or with the ChaCha system. When you access the Site or the Services, ChaCha’s servers may automatically track certain information about your use of the Site and the Services. This information may include your browser type and version, your IP address, any referring URL, any URLs you visit from the Site, and the time and date associated with, and the content of, any communications by, to or with the ChaCha system.

When you submit a search query or question using a mobile phone, mobile device or other phone-based query, ChaCha’s servers may record information including the originating telephone number, the service provider, the audible or text content of any communications with, by or to ChaCha and the time and date of the communications. ChaCha may link Personal Information provided by you through the Web with a telephone number designated by you if you register online and provide ChaCha with both your phone number and email address.

**Your Interaction with Guides**

ChaCha values its Guides greatly, but they are independent contractors, and ChaCha is not legally responsible for their actions in any manner. ChaCha instructs the Guides not to ask users for Personal Information and not to save any Personal Information derived from communications with users. ChaCha also instructs the Guides to act in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

You should not provide Personal Information to the Guides. If any Guide does ask you for any personally identifiable information or does anything else that raises a privacy concern, you may report any such abuse to ChaCha by use of the Contact link provided herein, as well as the Contact link located on the ChaCha homepage.

Information indicated in ChaCha’s logs may be presented to a Guide in order to improve the quality of the Services. Personal Information is not provided to a Guide except that for some queries, location information may be associated with the query and may be provided to a Guide for the purposes of providing or improving the service.

**Information Collected from Potential Guides**

A Guide may assist users of the Site and the Services. In ChaCha’s recruitment of Guides, ChaCha may collect and disseminate Personal Information from applications to become Guides that has been provided through the Site. If you provide Personal Information in order to seek work as a Guide, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, as well as the Terms of Use, which are incorporated herein by reference. On the basis of the Personal Information provided, ChaCha may contact you regarding potential work as a Guide. The Personal Information that you provide will not be sold, shared or otherwise distributed to any third parties outside ChaCha, except as necessary for purposes of identity verification, background checks, or as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, provided that, if you do become a Guide, use of Personal Information you provide will then be under a separate contract between you and ChaCha.

**Advertising and Links to other Web sites**

When you use the Site, a cookie may be sent to your browser. A cookie is a small text file sent by a website’s computer system that is stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are a commonly used technology on the Web, and they are used in ChaCha’s search functionality. You are always free to set your browser to decline cookies, and you can delete cookies from your computer. However, disabling cookies may adversely affect your ability to use the Site or the Services. See your browser’s “Help” file for more details on cookies.

ChaCha uses third party advertisers who serve ads and collect information on the Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on the Site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. These third party advertisers may also use cookies on this Site. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp . Further information regarding third party data collection and opt-out may be found at <http://youronlinechoices.eu/> .

Notwithstanding anything else in this Privacy Policy, ChaCha or a data provider we have engaged may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads or content. These cookies contain no personally identifiable information. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, (e.g., your email address), that ChaCha may share with a data provider solely in hashed, non-human readable form. To opt-out of these cookies, please go to <http://www.aboutads.info/choices> .

The Site and the Services may contain windows or hyperlinks which provide access to other websites not affiliated with ChaCha. Your use of an external website or any informational content found on an external website is subject to and governed by the terms and guidelines of said external website. ChaCha does not make any representations or warranties concerning, and will not in any way liable for, any informational content, products, services, software, or other materials available on an external website, even if one or more pages of the external website are framed within a page of the Site. ChaCha is not responsible for the privacy practices of any external website. For your protection, please refer to the privacy policies of the respective external websites. Access from Outside the United States

ChaCha stores and processes information in the United States of America. The data protection and privacy laws the United States may not be as protective as those in other countries, including, in particular, those in the European Union. By use of the Site and the Services, you expressly consent to the transfer of any information you provide to ChaCha for use in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**ChaCha’s Commitment to Data Security**

To improve data security and restrict access to your personal and business information, ChaCha has put in place certain physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard the information ChaCha collects via the Site. ChaCha does not, however, guarantee that information collected via the Site is or will be completely secure from misappropriation by hackers or from other dishonest or criminal activities, or in the event of a failure of computer hardware, software, or a telecommunications network.

**Compromise of Personal Information**

In the event that Personal Information is compromised as a result of a known or suspected breach of security, we will promptly notify those persons whose Personal Information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

**Notification Procedures**

It is ChaCha’s policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to our users via e-mail notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on our web site, as determined by us in our sole discretion. Notwithstanding the foregoing, we reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to our web site users.

**Third Party Disclosures**

This site uses ClickTale web analytics service. ClickTale may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity as well as any text you type in this website. ClickTale does not collect personally identifiable information that you do not voluntarily enter in this website. ClickTale does not track your browsing habits across web sites which do not use ClickTale services. For more information see Privacy Policy for Information Collected by the ClickTale Web Analytics Service. We are using the information collected by ClickTale service to optimize user experience.

You can choose to disable the Service at http://www.clicktale.net/disable.html.

**Deletion or Modification of Personal Information**

If you ever wish to access your Personal Information, or to have your Personal Information deleted, updated, changed or modified, you may contact ChaCha by mail, fax, or e-mail at the addresses indicated below:

**ChaCha Search, Inc.** **14550 Clay Terrace Blvd., Suite 130** **Carmel, IN 46032-3653**

**Fax: (317) 660-6687**

E-mail: [customer.relations@chacha.com](email:customer.relations@chacha.com)

Effective Date: June 10, 2014
